Guide to the Dorothy Porter Wesley Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Series I. Correspondence, 1870-2011
  - General Correspondence, Circa 1930-1996
    - Library of Congress, 1930-1995 (Box 44, Folder 395-396)
    - Lincoln University, 1932-1993 (Box 44, Folder 397)
    - Livraria J. Leite, 1945-1947 (Box 44, Folder 398)
    - Lloyd, Glaucia, 1973-1989 (Box 45, Folder 399)
    - Locke, Alain, 1885-1954, 1944- (Box 45, Folder 400)
    - Loeb, Ellen, 1962-1989 (Box 45, Folder 401)
    - Logan, Rayford Whittingham, 1897-1982, 1940-1993 (Box 45, Folder 402-403)
    - Los Angeles County Museum of Art, 1979-1996 (Box 45, Folder 404)
    - Lubin, Maurice, 1972-1993 (Box 45, Folder 405-406)
    - Lynn, Audrey, 1972-1993 (Box 45, Folder 407)
      - Empty, Undated (Box 45, Folder 408-409)
    - "M" General, Circa 1930-1996 (Box 46, Folder 410-415)
    - "M" General, Circa 1930-1996 (Box 47, Folder 416-418)
    - Mackey, Matilda, 1972-1975 (Box 47, Folder 419)
    - Mandara, Ramos, 1966-1968 (Box 47, Folder 420)
    - Marquis Who's Who, Inc., 1989- (Box 47, Folder 421)
    - Marteena, Constance, 1944-1945 (Box 47, Folder 422)
    - Mason, James, 1972-1985 (Box 47, Folder 423)
    - Matthews, Miriam, 1974-1994 (Box 47, Folder 424-425)
    - Mattingly, William, 1971-1979 (Box 47, Folder 426)
    - Maxwell, Hazel, 1972-1991 (Box 47, Folder 427)
    - McCants, Murville, 1981-1984 (Box 47, Folder 428)
    - McClellan, Wayland, 1987-1991 (Box 47, Folder 429)
    - McConnell, Catherine, 1986-1994 (Box 47, Folder 430)
    - McKay, Claude, 1890-1948, 1937- (Box 48, Folder 431)
    - McLemore, Roberta, 1932-1990 (Box 48, Folder 432)
    - McStallworth, Paul, 1986-1987 (Box 48, Folder 433)
    - Menard, Edith, 1985-1993 (Box 48, Folder 434)
    - Metraux, Alfred, 1935-1950 (Box 48, Folder 435)
    - Miles, Willie Leanna, 1985-1991 (Box 48, Folder 436)
    - Miller, Carroll, 1972-1995 (Box 48, Folder 437)
    - Miller, Nathan, 1973-1986 (Box 48, Folder 438)
    - Mingo, James, 1983-1993 (Box 48, Folder 439)
    - Minter, Thomas, 1977-1992 (Box 48, Folder 440)
    - Mooney, Jim, 1994- (Box 48, Folder 441)
    - Moore, Martha, 1989-1994 (Box 48, Folder 442)
    - Moore, Ruth, 1972-1986 (Box 49, Folder 443)
    - Moorland, Jesse Edward, 1863-1940, 1930-1940 (Box 49, Folder 444)
    - Moorland-Spingarn Research Center, 1971-1995 (Box 49, Folder 445-447)
    - Morgan State University, 1939-1977 (Box 49, Folder 448)
    - Morrow, Edward, 1975- (Box 49, Folder 449)
    - Mountainside Hospital (Montclair, N.J.), 1956-1957 (Box 49, Folder 450)
    - Museum of African Art, 1971-1982 (Box 49, Folder 451)
    - Myers, Ardie, 1992-1994 (Box 49, Folder 452)
    - "N" General, Circa 1930-1996 (Box 50, Folder 453-457)
    - National Afro-American Museum, 1982-1987 (Box 50, Folder 458)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1939-1993 (Box 50, Folder 459)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People Legal Defense and Educational Fund, 1953-1991 (Box 50, Folder 460)
    - National Council of Negro Women, 1939-1980 (Box 51, Folder 461-463)
    - National Caucus and Center on Black Aged (U.S.), 1991-1994 (Box 51, Folder 464)
    - National Association of Colored Women's Clubs (U.S.), 1960-1987 (Box 51, Folder 465-466)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1968-1994 (Box 51, Folder 467-469)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1968-1994 (Box 52, Folder 470)
    - National Museum of African Art, 1982-1992 (Box 52, Folder 471)
    - National Museum of American Art, 1984-1996 (Box 52, Folder 472)
    - National Museum of American History, 1985-1996 (Box 52, Folder 473)
    - National Portrait Gallery (Smithsonian Institution), 1973-1992 (Box 52, Folder 474)
    - National Urban League, 1981-1982 (Box 52, Folder 475)
    - Ndoh, Akon, 1985-1988 (Box 52, Folder 476)
    - Nelson, Blanche, 1946-1986 (Box 52, Folder 477)
    - Nelson, Minnie, 1993- (Box 52, Folder 478)
    - Neustadter, Griselda, 1977-1983 (Box 52, Folder 479)
    - Newbold, N. C. (Nathan Carter), 1871-1957, 1937- (Box 52, Folder 480)
    - Newlin, Eugenia Wilson, 1954-1962 (Box 52, Folder 481)
    - Newman, Richard, 1981-1989 (Box 52, Folder 482)
    - Newsome, Lionel, 1981-1988 (Box 52, Folder 483)
    - New York Public Library, 1931-1991 (Box 52, Folder 484)
    - Nigeria Liaison Office, 1960- (Box 52, Folder 485)
    - Nkrumah, Kwame, 1909-1972, 1962-1963 (Box 52, Folder 486)
    - North Carolina Central University, 1975-1995 (Box 53, Folder 487)
    - Northwestern University, 1945-1982 (Box 53, Folder 488)
    - Notable American Women, 1968-1977 (Box 53, Folder 489)
    - Nwanya, Jemima N., 1966-1981 (Box 53, Folder 490)
    - "O" General, Circa 1930-1995 (Box 54, Folder 491-492)
    - Oakwood School, 1953-1980 (Box 54, Folder 493)
    - Obi, Dorothy, 1966-1994 (Box 54, Folder 494-495)
    - Odester, Geraldine, 1974-1975 (Box 54, Folder 496)
    - Ogunnaike, Rex Kola, 1966-1970 (Box 54, Folder 497)
    - Ohio Historical Society, 1973-1986 (Box 54, Folder 498)
    - Okene College of Commerce, 1972-1978 (Box 54, Folder 499)
    - Olafioye, Olu A., 1964-1966 (Box 54, Folder 500)
    - O'neal, Charlotte, 1972-1990 (Box 54, Folder 501)
    - Organization of American Historians, 1978-1979 (Box 54, Folder 502)
    - "P" General, Circa 1930-1995 (Box 55, Folder 503-509)
    - "P" General, Circa 1930-1995 (Box 56, Folder 510-512)
    - Pace, Donis, 1972-1975 (Box 56, Folder 513)
    - Page, Ethel, 1968-1995 (Box 56, Folder 514-516)
    - Page, Kathy, 1986-1987 (Box 56, Folder 517)
    - Parker, Barrington, 1981-1995 (Box 56, Folder 518-519)
    - Partington, Paul, 1961-1991 (Box 57, Folder 520-522)
    - The Patriots Foundation, 1994-1995 (Box 57, Folder 523)
    - Penn, Rosalynn, 1975-1988 (Box 57, Folder 524)
    - Perry, Thelma, 1988-1995 (Box 57, Folder 525)
    - Petry, Ann, 1908-1997, 1981-1990 (Box 57, Folder 526)
    - Phelps-Stokes Fund, 1971-1991 (Box 57, Folder 527-528)
    - Phinazee, Hoage Annette, 1968-1973 (Box 57, Folder 529)
    - Pielage, Jozef, 1971-1992 (Box 58, Folder 530)
    - Pierce, Delilah, 1971-1984 (Box 58, Folder 531)
    - Pilgrim Society, 1973-1974 (Box 58, Folder 532)
    - Pinkett, Harold, 1980-1994 (Box 58, Folder 533)
    - Pollack, Helen, 1959-1973 (Box 58, Folder 534)
    - Pool, Rosey E., 1961-1970 (Box 58, Folder 535)
    - Porter, Lilian, 1941-1995 (Box 58, Folder 536)
    - Price, Charlotte S., 1932-1994 (Box 58, Folder 537-538)
    - Price, Charlotte S., 1932-1994 (Box 59, Folder 539-542)
    - Price, Charlotte S., 1984-1993 (Box 118 (Oversize), Folder 967)
    - Prior, Kathy, 1985- (Box 59, Folder 543)
    - Pryde, Marion J., 1988-1995 (Box 59, Folder 544)
    - Pryor, Chester, 1977-1990 (Box 59, Folder 545)
    - "Q" General, Circa 1930-1995 (Box 60, Folder 546)
    - Quarles, Benjamin, 1970-1995 (Box 60, Folder 547-548)
    - Queen, Curtis, 1972-1982 (Box 60, Folder 549)
    - "R" General, Circa 1930-1995 (Box 61, Folder 550-555)
    - Radcliffe College, 1977-1995 (Box 62, Folder 556-557)
    - Randall, Phillip, 1981-1982 (Box 62, Folder 558)
    - Raphael, Alex, 1972-1994 (Box 62, Folder 559)
    - Reid, Anna, 1979-1990 (Box 62, Folder 560)
    - Reimherr, Beulah, 1960-1994 (Box 62, Folder 561-562)
    - Reimherr, Beulah, 1960-1994 (Box 63, Folder 563-564)
    - Reimherr, Joyce, 1974-1992 (Box 63, Folder 565)
    - Rhodes, Leila, 1974-1982 (Box 63, Folder 566)
    - Richardson, Marilyn, 1983-1994 (Box 63, Folder 567)
    - Ridgleu, Louis, 1980-1984 (Box 63, Folder 568)
    - Ridley, Florida, 1939-1941 (Box 63, Folder 569)
    - Robinson, Henry, 1972-1987 (Box 63, Folder 570)
    - Robinson, Hilyard, 1968-1986 (Box 63, Folder 571)
    - Robinson, Marian, 1981-1995 (Box 64, Folder 572-573)
    - Rosenkranz, Joel, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 574)
    - Russell, Wendell, 1972-1975 (Box 64, Folder 575)
    - Rutgers University, 1963-1973 (Box 64, Folder 576)
    - "S" General, Circa 1930-1996 (Box 65, Folder 577-583)
    - "S" General, Circa 1930-1996 (Box 66, Folder 584-586)
    - SALAM (Seminar in the Acquisition of Latin American Library Materials), 1973-1974 (Box 66, Folder 587)
    - Salem State College, 1990-1991 (Box 66, Folder 588)
    - Sales, Ruby, 1988- (Box 66, Folder 589)
    - Sallu, Rasaki Adegboyega, 1961-1971 (Box 66, Folder 590)
    - Sarale Owens Memorial Scholarship, 1982-1985 (Box 66, Folder 591)
    - Scally, Anthony, 1983- (Box 66, Folder 592)
    - Schecter, Melvin D., 1971-1992 (Box 66, Folder 593)
    - Schomburg, Arthur Alfonso, 1874-1938, 1931- (Box 66, Folder 594)
    - Schomburg Center for Research in Black Culture, 1984-1994 (Box 66, Folder 595)
    - Schuyler, Phillipa, 1952-1953 (Box 66, Folder 596)
    - Shaw, Esther, 1956- (Box 67, Folder 597)
    - Shepperson, George, 1972-1989 (Box 67, Folder 598)
    - Shockley, Ann, 1974-1994 (Box 67, Folder 599)
    - Sigma Pi Phi, 1984-1997 (Box 67, Folder 600)
    - Simpson, Randolph L., 1984-1987 (Box 67, Folder 601)
    - Singleton, Theresa A., 1984- (Box 67, Folder 602)
    - Sinnette, Elinor Des Verney, 1973-1987 (Box 67, Folder 603)
    - Sitzman, Glenn L., 1920-, 1964-1973 (Box 67, Folder 604)
    - Slaughter, Henry, 1935-1952 (Box 67, Folder 605)
    - Sloan, Ruth Catherine, 1949-1976 (Box 67, Folder 606)
    - Smiley, Gladys, 1972-1986 (Box 67, Folder 607)
    - Smith, Alonzo, 1967-1985 (Box 67, Folder 608)
    - Smith, Elise, 1974-1988 (Box 67, Folder 609)
    - Smith, Julia H., 1967-1980 (Box 67, Folder 610)
    - Smith Marie, 1952-1973 (Box 68, Folder 611)
    - The Smith-Mason Gallery of Art, 1974-1980 (Box 68, Folder 612)
    - Smithsonisan Institution, 1969-1993 (Box 68, Folder 613)
    - Society of American Archivists, 1962-1974 (Box 68, Folder 614)
    - Sodeinede, Titola, 1969-1995 (Box 68, Folder 615)
    - Southern Methodist University, 1969-1996 (Box 68, Folder 616)
    - Spady, James, 1972-1992 (Box 68, Folder 617)
    - Spelman College, 1977-1993 (Box 68, Folder 618)
    - Spingarn, Arthur B. (Arthur Barnett), 1878-1971., 1930-1964 (Box 68, Folder 619)
    - Spingarn, Elizabeth, 1970-1979 (Box 68, Folder 620)
    - State of Alabama Historical Commission, 1975-1976 (Box 68, Folder 621)
    - Stauper, Mabel, 1971-1974 (Box 68, Folder 622)
    - Sterling, Dorothy, 1913-2008, 1968-1995 (Box 69, Folder 623-626)
    - Stewart, Donald, 1969-1995 (Box 69, Folder 627)
    - Stewart, Ethel P., 1968-1985 (Box 69, Folder 628)
    - Stewart, Ruth Ann, 1970-1991 (Box 69, Folder 629)
    - Stokes, Connie, 1961-1990 (Box 70, Folder 630-631)
    - Strong, Jake, 1981-1987 (Box 70, Folder 632)
    - Susquehenna Corporation, 1961-1983 (Box 70, Folder 633)
    - Susquehenna University, 1971-1995 (Box 70, Folder 634-635)
    - Syracuse University, 1979-1989 (Box 70, Folder 636-637)
    - "T" General, Circa 1930-1996 (Box 71, Folder 638-643)
    - Taylor, Ordie, 1980-1983 (Box 71, Folder 644)
    - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association of America, 1948-1986 (Box 71, Folder 645)
    - Temple University, 1972-1992 (Box 72, Folder 646)
    - Terborg-Penn, Rosalyn, 1981-1995 (Box 72, Folder 647)
    - Thornhill, Arthur, 1932-1985 (Box 72, Folder 648)
    - Thompson, H.M., 1980-1984 (Box 72, Folder 649)
    - Thurman, Howard, 1937-1962 (Box 72, Folder 650)
    - Thurman, Sue Bailey, 1955-1981 (Box 72, Folder 651)
    - TransAfrica (Organization), 1988-1993 (Box 72, Folder 652)
    - "U" General, Circa 1930-1995 (Box 73, Folder 653-656)
    - United Negro College Fund, 1948-1990 (Box 74, Folder 657)
    - United States of America General Services Administration, 1973-1976 (Box 74, Folder 658)
    - Unitred States Department of Interior, 1973-1987 (Box 74, Folder 659)
    - University of California Irvine, 1973-1974 (Box 74, Folder 660)
    - University of California Los Angeles, 1976-1990 (Box 74, Folder 661)
    - University of Denver, 1971-1983 (Box 74, Folder 662)
    - University of Ghana, 1963-1967 (Box 74, Folder 663)
    - University of Iowa, 1969-1991 (Box 74, Folder 664)
    - University of Maryland, 1967-1995 (Box 74, Folder 665)
    - University of Massachusettes Press, 1967-1995 (Box 74, Folder 666)
    - University of Michigan, 1980-1981 (Box 74, Folder 667-668)
    - University of Michigan, 1981- (Box 118 (Oversize), Folder 968)
    - University Microfilms, 1968- (Box 75, Folder 669)
    - Unniversity of Minnesota, 1975-1983 (Box 75, Folder 670)
    - University of Mississippi, 1985-1990 (Box 75, Folder 671)
    - University of Nigeria, 1962-1969 (Box 75, Folder 672)
    - University of North Carolina Chapel Hill, 1936-1988 (Box 75, Folder 673)
    - University of Pennsylvania, 1976-1989 (Box 75, Folder 674)
    - University of Rochester Library, 1978-1979 (Box 75, Folder 675)
    - University of Utah, 1989- (Box 75, Folder 676)
    - University of Virginia, 1981-1991 (Box 75, Folder 677)
    - University of Wisconson Whitewater, 1975-1988 (Box 75, Folder 678)
    - "V" General, Circa 1930-1995 (Box 76, Folder 679)
    - Vail, Robert, 1931-1945 (Box 76, Folder 680)
    - VanJackson, Wallace, 1944-1976 (Box 76, Folder 681)
    - Van Slycke and Reeside, Circa 1960 (Box 76, Folder 682)
    - Veiga, Winifred, 1959-1962 (Box 76, Folder 683)
    - Veuezky, Alice, 1972-1973 (Box 76, Folder 684)
    - Villard, Oswald G., 1939- (Box 76, Folder 685)
    - Virginia State College, 1962-1964 (Box 76, Folder 686)
    - Virginia Union University, 1936-1939 (Box 76, Folder 687)
    - "W" General, Circa 1930-1995 (Box 77, Folder 688-693)
    - "W" General, Circa 1930-1995 (Box 78, Folder 694-697)
    - Walker, William, 1944-1945 (Box 78, Folder 698)
    - War Department Office of the Chief of the Morale Branch, 1941- (Box 78, Folder 699)
    - Washington, D.C. March of Dimes, 1976- (Box 78, Folder 700)
    - The Washington Girl Friends, 1957- (Box 78, Folder 701)
    - The Washington Urban League Inc., 1992- (Box 78, Folder 702)
    - Washington, Walter, 1973-1987 (Box 79, Folder 703)
    - Watkins, Charlotte, 1985- (Box 79, Folder 704)
    - Watkins, Mark H., 1980-1986 (Box 79, Folder 705)
    - Watts, Faulkner, 1980-1986 (Box 79, Folder 706)
    - WGBH Educational Foundation, 1979-1987 (Box 79, Folder 707)
    - White, Carl, 1962-1966 (Box 79, Folder 708)
    - White, Herbert, 1979-1982 (Box 79, Folder 709)
    - The White House, 1994- (Box 79, Folder 710)
    - Whitney, Allan, 1968-1969 (Box 79, Folder 711)
    - Who's Who Among Black America, 1974-1991 (Box 79, Folder 712)
    - Wilkinson, Garnet Crummel, 1879-1969, 1931- (Box 79, Folder 713)
    - Williams, Charles, 1980-1986 (Box 79, Folder 714)
    - Williams, Lorraine, 1967-1990 (Box 79, Folder 715)
    - Winston, Michael, 1968-1995 (Box 80, Folder 716-719)
    - Woodson, Carter Godwin, 1875-1950, 1939-1949 (Box 80, Folder 720)
    - Workers Library Publishers, 1937-1949 (Box 80, Folder 721)
    - "Y" General, Circa 1960-1995 (Box 81, Folder 722)
    - Yale University, 1975-1986 (Box 81, Folder 723)
    - Yellin, Jean Fagan, 1979-1994 (Box 81, Folder 724-725)
    - Young, Pauline, 1874-1982 (Box 81, Folder 726)
    - Young, Wharton M., 1972-1987 (Box 81, Folder 727)
    - "Z" General, Circa 1970-1979 (Box 82, Folder 728)
    - Zohn, Arnold, 1968- (Box 82, Folder 729)
    - Invitations, Circa 1920-1960 (Box 83, Folder 730-734)
    - Invitations, Circa 1960-1970 (Box 84, Folder 735-742)
    - Invitations, Circa 1970 (Box 85, Folder 743-751)
    - Invitations, Circa 1970 (Box 86, Folder 752-758)
    - Invitations, Circa 1970 (Box 87, Folder 759-764)
    - Invitations, Circa 1970 (Box 88, Folder 765-771)
    - Invitations, Circa 1970 (Box 89, Folder 772-774)
    - Invitations, Circa 1980 (Box 90, Folder 775-778)
    - Invitations, Circa 1980 (Box 91, Folder 779-783)
    - Invitations, Circa 1980 (Box 92, Folder 784-790)
    - Invitations, Circa 1980 (Box 93, Folder 791-797)
    - Invitations, Circa 1980 (Box 94, Folder 798-802)
    - Invitations, Circa 1980 (Box 95, Folder 803-808)
    - Invitations, Circa 1980 (Box 96, Folder 809-813)
    - Invitations, Circa 1980 (Box 97, Folder 814-818)
    - Invitations, Circa 1990 (Box 98, Folder 819-823)
    - Invitations, Circa 1990 (Box 99, Folder 824-829)
    - Invitations, Circa 1990 (Box 100, Folder 830-835)
    - Invitations, Circa 1990 (Box 101, Folder 836-842)
    - Invitations, Circa 1990 (Box 102, Folder 843-849)
    - Invitations, Undated (Box 103, Folder 850-855)
    - Invitations, Undated (Box 104, Folder 856-859)
    - Unidentified Correspondence, Circa 1920-1995 (Box 105, Folder 860-866)
    - Unidentified Correspondence, Circa 1920-1995 (Box 106, Folder 867-871)
    - Unidentified Correspondence, Circa 1920-1995 (Box 107, Folder 872-877)
    - Unidentified Correspondence, Circa 1920-1995 (Box 108, Folder 878-882)
    - Unidentified Correspondence, Circa 1920-1995 (Box 109, Folder 883-886)
    - Empty Envelopes, Circa 1930-1996 (Box 110, Folder 887-892)
    - Empty Envelopes, Circa 1930-1996 (Box 111, Folder 893-895)
  - Third Party Correspondence, 1870-1978
    - Brooks, Edward to Knight, Nathaniel, 1975- (Box 112, Folder 896)
    - Cilluffo, Mary to Deal,Carl, 1975- (Box 112, Folder 897)
    - Clarke, J.B. to Spingarn Arthur B., 1968- (Box 112, Folder 898)
    - Cooley, Emma to Pritchard H.R., 1931- (Box 112, Folder 899)
    - Cunningham, Alice to Hull, Doris M., 1970- (Box 112, Folder 900)
    - Daniel, Walter G. to Boswell Arthur W., 1939- (Box 112, Folder 901)
    - Daniel Walter G. to Rushing, Naomi, Circa 1935-1945 (Box 112, Folder 902)
    - Dover, Cedric to Burke, Selma, 1959- (Box 112, Folder 903)
    - Eaton, John W. to Howard, Oliver Otis, 1969- (Box 112, Folder 904)
    - Ellis, Ethel M. to Reason, Joseph L., 1968- (Box 112, Folder 905)
    - Etia, Isaac Moume to Spingarn, Arthur B., 1935- (Box 112, Folder 906)
    - Fisher, Walter to Winston, Eric V.A., 1973- (Box 112, Folder 907)
    - Garrey, Barbara to Davis, Lenwood G., 1975- (Box 112, Folder 908)
    - Hood, Dorothy to Hill, Richard Hurst, 1937- (Box 112, Folder 909)
    - The Johns Hopkins Press to Kellog, C. Flint, 1968- (Box 112, Folder 910)
    - Johnson, Herbert Clay to Baithwaite, William S., 1947- (Box 112, Folder 911)
    - Jones, Clara to Cunningham William, 1973- (Box 112, Folder 912)
    - Knight, Nathanial B. to Members of the Washington Advisory Directorate, 1976- (Box 112, Folder 913)
    - Langford, Charlotte to Langford, James, 1936- (Box 112, Folder 914)
    - Miller, Kelly to Daniel, Walter G., 1938- (Box 112, Folder 915)
    - Moten, Robert R. to Chandler, Alice G., 1920- (Box 112, Folder 916)
    - Murry, Emma G. To Lathan W.W., 1931- (Box 112, Folder 917)
    - Rushing, Naomi J. to Duligard, Bessie, 1939- (Box 112, Folder 918)
    - Slowe, Lucy D. to Arthur, George R., 1930- (Box 112, Folder 919)
    - Smith, N. Clark to Lee, Jennie C., 1910- (Box 112, Folder 920)
    - Taylor, John W. to Dyson, Walter, 1930- (Box 112, Folder 921)
    - Thompson, Leon E. to Dove, Henry A., 1978- (Box 112, Folder 922)
    - Tillman, Benjamin R. to Forsyth T. S., 1913- (Box 112, Folder 923)
    - Vedder, Elihu to Murray, F.H. M., 1914- (Box 112, Folder 924)
    - Walker, George Leon to Adshead, G.H., 1886- (Box 112, Folder 925)
    - Weinberg, Samuel S. to Andrews, Richards, 1971- (Box 112, Folder 926)
    - Wilkerson, Doxey to Reed, Isabel, 1939- (Box 112, Folder 927)
    - Unidentified third party correspondence, 1870-1884 (Box 112, Folder 928)
  - Family Correspondence, Circa 1935-1996
    - Burnett, Gustee Willie
      - Wesley, Dorothy Porter, 1905-1995, 1936-1958 (Box 113, Folder 929)
    - Harper, Leonie
      - A-Z general, 1973-1987 (Box 113, Folder 930)
      - Wesley, Dorothy Porter, 1905-1995, 1956-1964 (Box 113, Folder 931)
    - Porter, James A. (James Amos), 1905-1970 (Box 113)
      - "C-H" General, 1960-1967 (Box 113, Folder 932)
      - Congress of the United States, 1965-1968 (Box 113, Folder 933)
    - Sadler, Roberta (Bertha) Burnett
      - C-W general, 1944-1961 (Box 113, Folder 934)
      - Wesley, Dorothy Porter, 1905-1995, 1935-1960 (Box 113, Folder 935)
    - Taylor, Alice
      - "A-U" General, 1965-1989 (Box 114, Folder 936-937)
      - Wesley, Dorothy Porter, 1905-1995, 1948-1989 (Box 114, Folder 938-939)
    - Uzelac, Constance Porter
      - "A-Y" General, Circa 1950-2011 (Box 115, Folder 940-949)
      - Wesley, Dorothy Porter, 1905-1995, 1950-1995 (Box 116, Folder 950-952)
      - Williams, Hazel, 1996- (Box 118 (Oversize), Folder 969)
      - Wyatt Houston Day Bookseller, 1997-2003 (Box 116, Folder 953)
      - Invitations, Circa 1950-2011 (Box 116, Folder 954)
      - Unidentified Correspondence, Circa 1950-2011 (Box 116, Folder 955)
      - Empty Envelopes, Circa 1950-2011 (Box 116, Folder 956)
    - Uzelac, Milan
      - Wesley, Dorothy Porter, 1905-1995, 1981-1984 (Box 116, Folder 957)
    - Wesley, Charles W.
      - "A-Z" General, 1949-1990 (Box 117, Folder 958-959)
      - Association for the Study of African-American Life and History, 1983-1984 (Box 117, Folder 960)
      - Wesley, Dorothy Porter, 1905-1995, 1935-1989 (Box 117, Folder 961)
- Series II. Professional Papers, 1869-2003
  Professional Papers is organized into three subseries: General; Speeches; and Writings.
  Professional Papers consists of materials related to the professional career of Dorothy Porter Wesley. General files include memorandums, notes and writings from committees and organizations Wesley was a member of including the Association for the study of African American Life and History, the National Council of Negro Women, the African American Materials Project, Federal Writers Project, the Ford Foundation, and the National Endowment for the Humanities. Also included are records from Wesley's tenure as librarian and curator at the Moorland-Spingarn Research Center including reports, and correspondence documenting book orders used to build the collection.
  Speeches document the lectures and remarks made by Wesley about librarianship and collections documenting the African Diaspora at universities such as Howard University, Boston University and Yale University. Writings consists of both published and unpublished bibliographies, essays, forewords and introductions on the subject of African, African American and Afro-Caribbean history and literature.It includes writings by Dorothy Porter Wesley James A. Porter, Charles H. Wesley, Constance Porter Uzelac; and a general assortment of writings by others.
  - General, 1869-2010
    - Ad Hoc Committee of Afro-Americans Concerned About U.S. Policy in Africa, 1970- (Box 119, Folder 970)
    - African American Institute, 1966-1967 (Box 119, Folder 971)
    - African American Materials Project (with correspondence from Annette Phinazee), 1971- (Box 119, Folder 972)
    - African American Museum Association Minutes and correspondence, 1980-1993 (Box 119, Folder 973-975)
    - African American Mosaic, 1970-1994 (Box 119, Folder 976)
    - African American Scholars Council, 1972-1975 (Box 119, Folder 977)
    - African American Scholars Council, 1973-1975 (Box 120, Folder 978)
    - African American Wives Group (Box 120, Folder 979)
    - African Imprint Library Services, 1972- (Box 120, Folder 980)
      - Oversize, 1972- (Box 178 (Oversize), Folder 1578)
    - African Journal of the International African Institute, 1964- (Box 120, Folder 981)
    - African Studies, 1960-1971 (Box 120, Folder 982)
      - Oversize, 1953-1964 (Box 178 (Oversize), Folder 1579)
    - African Studies Association, 1961-1993 (Box 120, Folder 983)
    - Afro-American Bicentennial Corporation, 1971-1975 (Box 120, Folder 984)
    - Afro-American Bicentennial Corporation, 1971-1975 (Box 121, Folder 985-989)
    - Afro-American Bicentennial Corporation, 1971-1975 (Box 122, Folder 990-993)
      - Oversize, 1974-1975 (Box 178 (Oversize), Folder 1580)
    - Afro-American Historical and Cultural Museum (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1976-1980 (Box 122, Folder 994)